rsdnation.com 2019-02-01

# PRIVACY POLICY - Real Social Dynamics Nation

#### 1\. **General Privacy Policy Information**

At Real Social Dynamics, we are 100% committed to protecting your privacy. We take online privacy seriously. We use state of the art software to protect you (“the customer”) from electronic fraud and other security issues. We never disclose the information to any agencies, nor do we sell the information that we may obtain from you. Please read on for more specific details of our privacy policy.

You linked to this Privacy Policy via a product website owned by Real Social Dynamics Corporation (“brand website”). This policy applies to all online communication with Real Social Dynamics owned brands. When you provide us with online information through this Website, we respect your privacy. It is important for you to understand what information we collect about you during your visit and what we do with that information. Please note that your visit to our Website is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions and that different policies may apply to information that we collect offline.

At all times, we reserve the right to disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; to protect Real Social Dynamics rights or property (including without limitation in the event of a transfer of control of a Real Social Dynamics company, affiliate, or brand, or substantially all of its assets), or during emergencies when safety is at risk, or for credit fraud protection and risk reduction purposes.

#### 2\. **Information Collection and Use**

When you sign up for any programs on the Real Social Dynamics Website, we need to know your name, e-mail address, and mailing address. This information allows us to establish an individual account for you. When you wish to purchase products, we need to know your credit card number and expiration date in order to process your transactions. These critical pieces of information are only for you to use and will not be given out to anyone else under any circumstances. We only collect personally identifiable information about you via this Website when you provide it in connection with a request for a product, service, or information. For example, if you decide to place an order, we will ask you for your delivery and billing address, phone number(s), email address, credit card number and its expiration date. If you decide to complete a user registration form or survey, we may ask you for information such as your contact information (e.g., name, e-mail address and mailing address), age group or birth date. When you submit your personally identifiable information on this Website, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. Real Social Dynamics companies may use the information that you provide to fulfill your request for a product, information, or other service, or respond to an email or other request, as well as to create and deliver to you our newsletters or surveys, communications containing product information, usage tips or promotions, help improve our website(s) or services, or customize visitors’ experience at our website(s). We do not share your credit card or other account information with unaffiliated third parties unless you authorize us to do so, or if it is necessary to fulfill our responsibilities including, but not limited to, delivering a product or service that you order. If you prefer not to receive email marketing communications from us or from third parties, please see Section 8 below. You cannot opt-out of receiving communications from Real Social Dynamics (or third parties who may assist us) relating to a specific order or request for a product or service. If you would prefer that we not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any such information.

We may also collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of this Website, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular. Information gathered may be used in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We may share or transfer such aggregate, non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees and partners.

This Website is intended for adults. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. However, if the parent or guardian of a child under 13 believes that the child has provided us with personally identifiable information, the parent or guardian of that child should contact us at [admin@realsocialdynamics.com](mailto:admin@realsocialdynamics.com) if they want this information deleted from our files so that it is not in retrievable form. If we otherwise obtain knowledge that we have personally identifiable information about a child under 13 in retrievable form in our files, we will delete that information from our existing files so that it is not retrievable.

#### 3\. **Ensuring Your Security**

We use the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an advanced security protocol that protects your credit card information and ensures secure online ordering. SSL Internet connections are encrypted, and thus protect all credit card ordering information, including your name, address and credit card number, so no one can read it in transit. We use secure technology, privacy protection controls, and restrictions on employee access, to safeguard your personal information.

#### 4\. **Safe Shopping Guarantee**

We guarantee that every online transaction you make will be “100% safe”. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at our online store. It is determined that under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, we will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.

#### 5\. **Technology Utilized**

There are two commonly used technologies used on this site, clear gifs and cookies. We use these to monitor the performance of the site and to measure it’s effectiveness. “Cookies” are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We do not use cookies to obtain any personally identifying information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent this. Please be assured that accepting a cookie does not give us access to your computer or personal information under any circumstances. If you disable cookies, you may be unable to order or use other features of our sites. If you experience any problems, please email us at [admin@realsocialdynamics.com](mailto:admin@realsocialdynamics.com).

Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs are not tied to users’ personally identifiable information but just tell us if you may have seen one of our ads online.

#### 6\. **Third Parties**

We may rely on other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include data analysis firms, customer support specialists, web-hosting companies, and fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that fill product orders or coordinate mailings). We may share personally identifiable information with such third parties as appropriate for them to perform their functions, but they may not use such information for any other purpose. We may also share personally identifiable information with marketing partners or other direct marketers, so they can send you notices about their products or services. If you do not want to receive email-marketing communications, see section 8 below for opt-out information.

#### 7\. **Notification of Changes**

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy.

#### 8\. **Real Social Dynamics Strict Email Policy**

Real Social Dynamics does not send any unsolicited e-mail and strives to adhere to the following guidelines as offered by Mail Abuse Prevention Systems (MAPS), LLC., an Internet e-mail watchdog association. If you’d like to be excluded from this our e-mail list, please [admin@realsocialdynamics.com](mailto:admin@realsocialdynamics.com).

Real Social Dynamics provides a simple method for subscribers to terminate their subscriptions. We have multiple automated “opt-out” functions on our site, and always include unsubscribe information in our mailings. Mailings from our lists cease promptly once a subscription is terminated.

Real Social Dynamics provides numerous alternative methods for terminating a subscription. We provide numerous “out of band” procedures for those who wish to terminate their mailing list subscriptions but are either unable or unwilling to follow standard automated procedures.

Real Social Dynamics takes numerous steps to prevent use of our mailing list for abusive purposes. We take adequate steps to ensure that our lists cannot be used for these purposes. We maintain a permanent “exclusion list” of e-mail addresses from which all subscription requests are rejected. Addresses are added to the exclusion list upon request by the parties entitled to use the addresses at issue. The purpose of the exclusion list is to prevent a forged subscription of an address by unauthorized third parties.

Real Social Dynamics always uses acquired or rented lists for their original purpose. When acquiring or renting verified opt-in lists, we closely examine the terms and conditions under which the addresses were originally compiled. We independently determine that all recipients have in fact opted-in to the type individual mailing that we intend to deliver.

Real Social Dynamics discloses the nature and frequency of mailings that it intends to send. We make adequate disclosures about the nature of our mailings, including the subject matter and anticipated frequency of messages.

Real Social Dynamics adheres to a strict “One Subscription, One List” Policy. Addresses are not added to other lists without fully verified consent of the address owner. We never assume that subscribers to our list wants to be added to another list.

#### 9\. **Your Thoughts Count**

Real Social Dynamics welcomes your questions and comments about privacy and all other topics as well. Please send your comments via e-mail to [admin@realsocialdynamics.com](mailto:admin@realsocialdynamics.com).

#### 10\. **Real Social Dynamics Privacy Summary**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information that we collect to make attending Real Social Dynamics programs possible and to allow customers to purchase products from Real Social Dynamics.

We do not sell, rent, or trade your personal information to others under any circumstance, and we will always continue this practice in the future. By using Real Social Dynamics, you consent to the collection and internal use of this information by Real Social Dynamics.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. We may use information such as e-mail addresses to alert our customers of special promotions that we may be running or to inform you of any news. To update your current preferences for receiving email marketing from us or marketing partners, you may click the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any e-mail you receive from a Real Social Dynamics company or email [admin@realsocialdynamics.com](emailto:admin@realsocialdynamics.com).

We will make every reasonable effort to respect your contact wishes. Please be aware that information does flow from a variety of channels that may sometimes cause your opt-out wishes to be delayed. In the event you feel you are contacted and should not have been, please contact us [admin@realsocialdynamics.com](mailto:admin@realsocialdynamics.com).
